ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) /3070
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.)
1948-1966
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3070
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
8436569
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 13, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3066: ILR School Alumni News /3069: ILR School School Scrapbook /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3073 PUBS: ILR School "Voice of Ives Hall" and "ILR Voice" Publications /3074 PUBS: ILR School "ILR Newsletter" and Other Student Publications /3075 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Student Publications /4185: ILR School Additional Publications /4252m: ILR School Student publication "The Cornell Worker" /4253m: ILR School Student Publication "Solidarity: Cornell's Pro-Labor Voice" /4264 PUBS: ILR School Communications Department Publications
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436569
- NYSSILR Cornell University For Our Information Version 1, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- NYSSILR Cornell University For Our Information Version 2, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 3, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 4, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 5, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 6, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 3, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 8, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 9, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 10, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 11, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 12-13, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NYSSILR Cornell University - For Our Information Version 14-15, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1951 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1957 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 1960 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)